There's 104 days of summer vacation and school comes along just to end the annual problem
Creating
As you can see there's a whole lot of stuff
Mom Phineas and Ferb are making a title sequence
So Ferb what do you want to do today
What about Perry what does he want to do
Well he's a platypus they don't do much iPhone when I'm starting to get bored and boredom is something up with which I will not put the person they're going to ask us when we get back to school with one of these do over summer
I mean no school for 3 months while I should be a roller coaster and I mean a good roller coaster
Not like that when we were at the State Fair
I know we're going to do today I'm going to go pick up a few things you boys out of trouble okay
Okay Mom we're going to build a roller coaster I'm in charge right
You did tell them I'm in charge relax Candice nobody has to be in charge emergency like what what is a satellite falls out of orbit impressionism
If that happens you're in charge whenever wait a minute what are you doing
It's summer that's cool you wait till last minute then well I'm watching you
And I'm in charge
Hello
No I can't go to the mall right now she left me in charge plug-in conditionally can you see if Jeremy is there a cheeseburger
Yeah he told me last time I was there I just about died it I told you I can't and watch my brother and step-brother
Mom left me in charge so they'll be no Shenanigans today we're leaving right now what do you ask what do you mean you could see it from your house
Phineas what is this you like I'm going to go tell Mommy when she sees what you are doing you are going down down down down
Call Debby Ryan.
We're going to need a blowtorch and some more peanut butter
Case Aeneas Isabella doing a roller coaster in your backyard some of it loud It's kind of impossible some would say
Say hey Ferb
The sister brother ever talk
Ignore the man of action
I was going to go to the pool you want to go swimming kind of in the middle of something here right okay I'll see you later then okay you got enough
The bear
Hey where's Perry
The evil doctor
Recent top 80% of the country's tinfoil I want you to get over to his Hideout right away find out what he's up to and put a stop to it as part of your cover identity
We're all counting on you
The way I see it taken in the mall parking lot
I'm going to go get the snakes you got to come home right now to the house no no no
Phineas and Ferb are doing it seems like we've had this conversation before I seem to recall you telling me that the boys were training monkeys to juggle bicycles and when I came home there was a stunning lack of monkeys
Don't know how to clean up so fast so what's the emergency this time building a roller coaster Candace seriously Phineas little young to be a roller coaster engineer
Aren't you a little young to be a roller coaster engineer
Affordable seem to be in order although I never seen them filled out in crayon before so if there's anything I can get you anything at all just let me know
Now this is the life
Unexpected surprise and by unexpected I mean
Dr. Heinz Doofenshmirtz the entire Eastern Seaboard in tin foil and when I put my Giant
Magnetism magnifier directions
Ask yourself what could we possibly have
I mean a lot
Open mom Phineas and Ferb at a rollercoaster you think we get a discount if we bring the flyer
And you're not crazy because I see your point Candace no crazy person would scream at a post like that I'll be in the dairy section if you want to come yell at some cheese or anything
Ladies and gentlemen boys and girls children of all ages
May I present to you expect the most of the morning in the making the coolest coaster ever
So who wants to go first to fasten insert the tab into the metal buckle to release just pull back on us
Well that's about it enjoy the ride you won't sign the waivers right
Viber
Make all my money back
Imaginable electromagnetic forces
Now I know I have that clubcard in here somewhere I always have it with me but my purse is such a disaster area
Okay I give up what am I
Am I supposed to be looking at I'm going to go get the cart time to go I've got Frozen
Frozen so you think are still under that stupid tree the backyard right that would be my guess.
Funny I remember this is a blueprint and I'm sure this is Niall
I worry about you sometimes Candace
Anyone want fries
Crush dearth Kansas in charge
Do charge more
Okay we're here are you happy now and I told you they weren't there
Hi Mom
Come on Candice help me with the groceries let's go
JCPenney's have a great way to cool awesome so what are you going to do
Tomorrow don't know yet maybe you can teach Perry some tricks will he's a platypus they don't do much are the only mammals that lay eggs
City Hall Annex
See you tomorrow it really was the coolest coaster ever you guys make a great team while a brother is a brother but I couldn't have asked for a better one than Ferb
You know what I mean old man I can smell the peanut butter that was impressive see you guys so what should we do tomorrow
There's a world of possibilities maybe we should make a list
Paper for his birthday
We got to do better than last year not our best work this time it's got to be something huge
Micropenis
Perry
This is yours I believe happy birthday Candice
I made you a special breakfast after that we have a surprise we have to drive to it
No wait please don't tell me
Tell me we're going to Mount Rushmore rate for American presidents carved into the side of a mountain that was Phineas and Ferb's idea you're welcome
Okay you look coming ahead I'll find a parking spot to meet you there okay we'll join you in a minute okay
Okay Candice it's your birthday you can pick out anything you want what about the Mount Rushmore bobblehead Mom that's playing okay how about this cute cut
Cuddle me Lincoln Jeremy hi Jeremy Janice what are you doing here
It's my birthday today and
Where they go
Hanford at the monument possibilities hey
At Mount Rushmore I know you were just there for planning on our part actually sorry
Hey honey what are you doing
Doing up on the monument let me see that you've got to see this now here book
Ran out of time
Old Reliable geyser how exciting go back to the gift shop
Your timing is impeccable impeccable I mean
Team
As they say in China
Now
Where should we start Phineas what you doing it's a surprise can I help we could use a lookout you got it
Oh man if you handle the big stick you got it you got it
How to do a threesome for between
Excuse me but you boys a little young to be restoring a National Monument yes yes we are
Go to see young people taking an interest in our National Heritage
Completely slipped my mind
Are you coming weekly see what those two are up to she's coming
It's getting closer running a little behind schedule go to plan B
You are shocked by what I'm about to show you Mom
I guess some things look better in photos it's Dad hi honey in space
Great I'll meet you at the gift shop Deer I still have to buy that big stick now
Oops
Right now are you still trying to get the boys in trouble anyways every set for me
You know Candice this is the second time I've climbed up there I'm already down half a dress size
Finally made it honey what is it you wanted me to see
You're right it's beautiful happy birthday honey
Now let's go find your father did you like your birthday present
Well it was definitely better than the gorilla in the cake
Hey Candice I am breaking I I thought I'd give you this for your birthday I saw you looking at in the gift shop at Mount Rushmore bobblehead you like it
I absolutely love it I got to get back on birthday
This was the best birthday ever