♪ AND THEN SCHOOL COMES ALONG
JUST TO END IT ♪
♪ SO THE ANNUAL PROBLEM
FOR OUR GENERATION ♪
♪ IS FINDING A GOOD WAY
TO SPEND IT ♪
♪ LIKE MAYBE
♪ BUILDING A ROCKET
♪ OR FIGHTING A MUMMY
♪ OR CLIMBING UP
THE EIFFEL TOWER ♪
HEY!
♪ DISCOVERING SOMETHING
THAT DOESN'T EXIST ♪
♪ OR GIVING A MONKEY A SHOWER
♪ SURFING TIDAL WAVES
♪ OR LOCATING
FRANKENSTEIN'S BRAIN ♪
IT'S OVER HERE.
♪ FINDING A DODO BIRD
♪ OR DRIVING
YOUR SISTER INSANE ♪
PHINEAS!
♪ THERE'S A WHOLE LOT
OF STUFF TO DO ♪
♪ BEFORE SCHOOL STARTS
THIS FALL ♪
♪ SO STICK WITH US
'CAUSE PHINEAS AND FERB ♪
♪ ARE GONNA DO IT ALL
♪ SO STICK WITH US
'CAUSE PHINEAS AND FERB ♪
♪ ARE GONNA DO IT ALL
MOM! PHINEAS AND FERB
ARE MAKING A TITLE SEQUENCE!
SO, FERB, WHAT DO YOU
WANT TO DO TODAY?
WHAT ABOUT PERRY?
WHAT DOES HE WANT TO DO?
[CHATTERING]
WELL, HE'S A PLATYPUS.
THEY DON'T DO MUCH.
I FOR ONE AM STARTING
TO GET BORED,
AND BOREDOM IS SOMETHING
UP WITH WHICH I WILL NOT PUT.
WHEN WE GET BACK TO SCHOOL
IS WHAT DID WE DO OVER SUMMER?
I MEAN, NO SCHOOL
FOR 3 MONTHS,
OUR LIFE SHOULD BE
A ROLLERCOASTER.
AND I MEAN
A GOOD ROLLERCOASTER.
NOT LIKE THAT ONE WE RODE
AT THE STATE FAIR.
[ROLLERCOASTER RUMBLING]
AAH!
PLEASE EXIT TO THE LEFT.
WHY, IF I BUILT
A ROLLERCOASTER, I WOULD--
THAT'S IT! I KNOW WHAT
WE'RE GONNA DO TODAY.
PHINEAS, FERB,
I'M GONNA GO PICK UP
A FEW THINGS.
YOU BOYS STAY OUT
OF TROUBLE, OK?
WE'RE GONNA BUILD
A ROLLERCOASTER.
YOU DID TELL THEM
I'M IN CHARGE?
RELAX, CANDACE.
NOBODY HAS TO BE IN CHARGE.
BUT WHAT IF THERE'S
AN EMERGENCY?
LIKE WHAT?
WHAT IF A SATELLITE
FALLS OUT OF ORBIT
AND CRASHES
INTO THE HOUSE?!
IF THAT HAPPENS,
YOU'RE IN CHARGE.
MOM SAYS I'M IN CHARGE
CONDITIONALLY.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HOMEWORK.
THAT'S COOL. YOU WAIT
TILL THE LAST MINUTE, THEN.
WELL, I'M WATCHING YOU.
AND I'M IN CHARGE.
CONDITIONALLY!
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
HELLO?
NO, I CAN'T GO
TO THE MALL RIGHT NOW.
MOM JUST WENT
TO THE STORE.
SHE LEFT ME IN CHARGE.
NO, NO, HE'S THE CUTE ONE
THAT WORKS AT
MR. SLUSHY BURGER.
YEAH, HE TOTALLY SMILED AT ME
THE LAST TIME I WAS THERE.
I JUST ABOUT DIED.
I'M WATCHING MY BROTHER
AND STEPBROTHER.
YEAH, AND THEY NEVER
GET INTO TROUBLE
BECAUSE MOM NEVER
CATCHES THEM.
ONE OF THESE DAYS, THOUGH,
I'M GONNA SEE TO IT
THAT SHE CATCHES THEM
RED-HANDED.
[ROAR]
WILL YOU HOLD IT DOWN!
I AM TRYING
TO USE THE PHONE!
SO THERE WILL BE
NO SHENANIGANS TODAY.
WHAT ARE THEY DOING
RIGHT NOW?
WHY DO YOU ASK?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
YOU CAN SEE IT
FROM YOUR HOUSE?
SEE WHAT?!
PHINEAS, WHAT IS THAT?
OOH, I'M GONNA GO TELL MOM,
AND WHEN SHE SEES
WHAT YOU ARE DOING,
YOU ARE GOING DOWN!
DOWN, DOWN, DOWN!
D-O-W-N! DOWN!
WE'RE GONNA NEED A BLOWTORCH
AND SOME MORE PEANUT BUTTER.
HEY, CANDACE,
IS PHINEAS--
HOME?
DOOM. DOWN, I SAY.
HEY, PHINEAS.
WHATCHA DOIN'?
HEY, ISABELLA.
BUILDING A ROLLERCOASTER.
IN YOUR BACKYARD?
WOW. ISN'T THAT
KIND OF IMPOSSIBLE?
SOME MIGHT SAY.
HEY, FERB.
DOES YOUR STEPBROTHER
EVER TALK?
FERB? HE'S MORE OF
A MAN OF ACTION.
I WAS GONNA
GO TO THE POOL.
KIND OF IN THE MIDDLE
OF SOMETHING HERE.
OK. I'LL SEE YOU
LATER, THEN.
HEY, FERB, YOU GOT
ENOUGH RIVETS UP THERE?
WHEW.
HEY, WHERE'S PERRY?
GOOD MORNING, AGENT P.
THE EVIL DR. DOOFENSCHMIRTZ
IS UP TO HIS OLD TRICKS.
HE'S BOUGHT UP 80%
OF THE COUNTRY'S TINFOIL.
I WANT YOU TO GET OVER
TO HIS HIDEOUT RIGHT AWAY,
FIND OUT WHAT HE'S UP TO,
AND PUT A STOP TO IT.
AS ALWAYS, AGENT P,
IT IS IMPERATIVE
THAT YOUR COVER IDENTITY
AS A MINDLESS DOMESTIC PET
REMAINS INTACT.
NOW GET OUT THERE.
WE'RE ALL COUNTING ON YOU.
♪ DOOBY DOOBY DOO BA DOO
♪ DOOBY DOOBY DOO BA
THEN WE RELEASE THE SNAKES
DURING THE CORKSCREW
AROUND THE INTERSTATE.
I'M GONNA GO GET
THE SNAKES.
MOM, YOU'VE GOTTA
COME HOME RIGHT NOW.
NO, NO, NO!
YOU GOTTA SEE WHAT
PHINEAS AND FERB RE DOING.
IT SEEMS LIKE WE'VE HAD
THIS CONVERSATION BEFORE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
AND WHEN I CAME HOME,
THERE WAS A STUNNING
LACK OF MONKEYS.
I STILL DON'T KNOW HOW
THEY CLEANED IT UP SO FAST.
SO WHAT'S THE EMERGENCY
THIS TIME?
CANDACE, SERIOUSLY,
ISN'T PHINEAS A LITTLE YOUNG
TO BE A ROLLERCOASTER
ENGINEER?
AREN'T YOU A LITTLE YOUNG
TO BE A ROLLERCOASTER
ENGINEER?
YES. YES, I AM.
WELL, I MUST SAY,
I'M VERY IMPRESSED.
THE FORMS ALL SEEM
TO BE IN ORDER,
ALTHOUGH I'VE NEVER
SEEN THEM FILLED OUT
SO IF THERE'S ANYTHING
I CAN GET YOU,
DO YOU THINK WE COULD BORROW
ONE OF THOSE GADGETS?
NOW, THIS IS THE LIFE.
AH, PERRY THE PLATYPUS.
WHAT AN UNEXPECTED SURPRISE.
AND BY UNEXPECTED,
I MEAN
COMPLETELY EXPECTED!
I, DR. HEINZ DOOFENSCHMIRTZ,
HAVE COVERED THE ENTIRE
EASTERN SEABOARD
IN TINFOIL.
AND WHEN I PUT
MY GIANT MAGNET
NEXT TO MY INGENIOUS
MAGNETISM MAGNIFIER,
I WILL PULL THE EAST
IN A WESTERLY DIRECTION,
THEREBY REVERSING ROTATION
OF THE EARTH.
YOU MAY WELL ASK YOURSELF,
WHY WOULD HE DO THIS?
WHAT COULD HE POSSIBLY
HAVE TO GAIN?
WELL, LET ME
JUST ANSWER THAT BY SAYING
I HAVEN'T REALLY WORKED OUT
ALL THE BUGS YET,
BUT, MOM, I TELL YOU,
THEY'RE BUILDING IT
AND IT'S HUGE!
"PHINEAS AND FERB PRESENT
THE COOLEST COASTER EVER.
NOW OPEN." MOM!
YOU THINK WE GET A DISCOUNT
IF WE BRING THE FLIER?
I THINK
WE BETTER TAKE IT.
HERE. LOOK, LOOK, LOOK.
SEE?
I TOLD YOU I'M NOT CRAZY.
I TOLD YOU.
AND YOU'RE NOT CRAZY
BECAUSE...
NO CRAZY PERSON
WOULD SCREAM AT A POST
LIKE THAT.
IF YOU WANT TO COME
YELL AT SOME CHEESE
OR ANYTHING.
[MICROPHONE SQUEALS]
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
BOYS AND GIRLS,
CHILDREN OF ALL AGES.
MAY I PRESENT TO YOU
A SPECTACLE
MOST OF THE MORNING
IN THE MAKING,
THE COOLEST...
COASTER...
EVER!
[BIRD SQUAWKING]
[AWK]
[CLANK]
SO, WHO WANTS TO GO FIRST?
TO FASTEN, INSERT THE TAB
INTO THE METAL BUCKLE.
TO RELEASE,
JUST PULL BACK ON THE--OOPS.
WELL, YOU GET THE PICTURE.
WELL, THAT'S ABOUT IT.
ENJOY THE RIDE.
YOU ALL SIGNED
THE WAIVERS, RIGHT?
AAH!
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
RELAX,
THEY'RE JUST RUBBER.
[SQUEAK SQUEAK]
[SCREAMING]
HEY, LOOK, HERE COMES
THE AAH-AAH-AAH-AAH.
All: AAH-AAH-AAH-AAH!
BUT I REALLY MAKE
ALL MY MONEY BACK.
I--I--I COULD BUY
A BUNCH OF EAST-FACING
REAL ESTATE
AND SELL IT AGAIN
WITH A...[MUTTERING]
HAH! YOU MISSED!
OW!
OW-OW-OW-OW!
OWW!
NOW, YOU ARE TOO
LATE!
QUAKE IN YOUR BOOTS
AND WATCH HELPLESSLY
AS THE UNIMAGINABLE
ELECTROMAGNETIC FORCES
PULL THE EASTERN SEABOARD,
THEREBY REVERSING
ROTATION OF THE EARTH.
WELL...THAT DIDN'T WORK.
AND NOW WE HAVE A 2-TON
BALL OF TINFOIL
TRAVELING 200 MILES AN HOUR
DIRECTLY AT US!
QUICKLY! WE MUST SEPARATE
THE MAGNET FROM THE MAGNIFIER
BEFORE IT IS TOO LATE!
I ALWAYS HAVE IT WITH ME,
BUT MY PURSE IS SUCH
A DISASTER AREA.
YOU KNOW HOW IT IS.
OH, OH, OH, OH! MOM!
MOM!
IT'S NO USE!
WE ARE DOOMED!
YOU SAVED US,
PERRY THE PLATYPUS!
BLESS YOU,
LOOK, LOOK, LOOK, LOOK!
SEE?
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO BE LOOKING AT?
NO! IT'S NOT POSSIBLE!
I'M GONNA GO
GET THE CART.
IT WAS RIGHT HERE
AND IT WAS HUGE!
TIME TO GO.
I'VE GOT FROZEN.
ARE STILL UNDER
THAT STUPID TREE
IN THE BACKYARD, RIGHT?
WELL, YES,
THAT WOULD BE MY GUESS.
FINE. THEN LET'S
GO HOME--NOW!
OH, THERE YOU ARE, PERRY.
[CHATTERING]
NICE HAT, ISABELLA.
HMM.
AAH!
[ALL SCREAMING]
FUNNY. I DON'T REMEMBER
THIS IN THE BLUEPRINTS.
AND I'M SURE THIS IS NEW.
HEE-HEE-HEE-HEE.
I WORRY ABOUT YOU
SOMETIMES, CANDACE.
WELCOME TO MR. SLUSHY BURGER.
MAY I TAKE YOUR ORDER?
ANYONE WANT FRIES?
CROISSANT?
ANYONE WANT A CROISSANT?
[BEEP BEEP BEEP]
YOU KNOW, IF THAT THING
CRASHES TO EARTH,
CANDACE IS IN CHARGE.
AAH!
[ALL SCREAMING]
WE SHOULD HAVE
CHARGED MORE.
OK, WE'RE HERE.
ARE YOU HAPPY NOW, CANDACE?
[GASPING AND LAUGHING]
YES! SEE, MOM? I TOLD YOU
THEY WEREN'T THERE.
HI, MOM.
OH, HI, BOYS.
COME ON, CANDACE,
HELP ME WITH THE GROCERIES.
B-B-B-B-BUT-BUT-BUT-BUT--
BUT--BUT--BUT--BUT--BUT--
HEY, PHINEAS,
THAT WAS GREAT.
WAY TOO COOL.
THAT WAS AWESOME!
SORRY. ONLY ONE RIDE
PER CUSTOMER.
THAT WAS GREAT,
PHINEAS.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO TOMORROW?
MAYBE YOU CAN TEACH
PERRY SOME TRICKS.
WELL, HE IS A PLATYPUS.
THEY'RE THE ONLY MAMMALS
TO LAY EGGS.
MAYBE HE'LL LAY AN EGG.
COOL.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
IT REALLY WAS THE COOLEST
COASTER EVER.
YOU GUYS MAKE A GREAT TEAM.
BUT I COULDN'T HAVE ASKED
FOR A BETTER ONE THAT FERB.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
OH, MAN! I CAN SMELL
THE PEANUT BUTTER.
WELL, THAT WAS IMPRESSIVE.
SEE YOU, GUYS.
SO WHAT SHOULD WE DO
TOMORROW?
THERE'S A WORLD
OF POSSIBILITIES.
MAYBE WE SHOULD
MAKE A LIST.
[BOOM]
[CAR ALARMS]
Candace: MOM!
GIVE IT A REST, CANDACE!
YES! HEY, FERB!
IT'S CANDACE'S BIRTHDAY.
WE'VE GOTTA DO BETTER
THAN LAST YEAR.
AAH!
[ROAR]
THIS TIME IT'S GOTTA BE
SOMETHING HUGE.
♪ SHE'S CANDACE
♪ LIKE THE VENUS DE MILO ♪
♪ EXCEPT SHE'S NOT ARMLESS
AND HANDLESS ♪
♪ SHE'S GOT A BIG
HONKIN' TRUCKLOAD ♪
♪ OF SHIP-LAUNCHIN' QUALITIES
♪ AND THIS IS THE REASON
♪ SHE BEARS NO RESEMBLANCE
TO A ♪
♪ PRAYING MANTIS
♪ A NAME WITH 7 LETTERS
♪ ONLY WEARS
DESIGNER SWEATERS ♪
♪ SHE'S GOT AN ALLERGY
TO DAIRY ♪
♪ AND SHE'S ANYTHING
BUT ORDINARY ♪
[CHATTERING]
PERRY?
THIS IS YOURS,
I BELIEVE.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, CANDACE.
I MADE YOU A SPECIAL
BREAKFAST.
AND AFTER THAT,
WE HAVE A SURPRISE.
WHAT IS IT?
WHERE IS IT?
WE HAVE TO DRIVE TO IT.
OOH-WHOO-OOH!
IS IT THE MALL?
OK. BUT IT'S THE MALL,
RIGHT?
WAIT. PLEASE DON'T TELL ME
WE'RE GOING TO MT. RUSHMORE.
ISN'T IT GREAT?
CARVED INTO THE SIDE
OF A MOUNTAIN.
IT WAS PHINEAS'
AND FERB'S IDEA.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
OK, YOU LOT GO ON AHEAD.
I'LL FIND A PARKING SPOT
AND MEET YOU THERE.
WE'RE GOING UP TO
THE MONUMENT.
COME ON, PERRY.
OK. WE'LL JOIN YOU
IN A MINUTE.
OK, CANDACE,
IT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY.
YOU CAN PICK OUT
ANYTHING YOU WANT.
OOH! WHAT ABOUT
THE MT. RUSHMORE
BOBBLEHEAD?
MOM, THAT'S LAME.
OK. HOW ABOUT
THIS CUTE,
CUDDLY LINCOLN?
[GASP] JEREMY?
HI, JEREMY.
HEY, CANDACE.
OH, I'M JUST HERE
ON THE MR. SLUSHY BURGER
WORKER EXCHANGE PROGRAM.
UM...
UH--OH--WELL,
IT'S MY BIRTHDAY TODAY,
AND...I...UH...
I GOTTA CHECK SOMETHING.
BACK IN A FLASH, OK?
WHERE DID THEY GO?
HI, MRS. FLETCHER.
OH, HI, ISABELLA.
WHAT BRINGS
YOU GIRLS HERE?
FIRESIDE GIRLS
FIELD TRIP.
UM...IS PHINEAS HERE?
MM-HMM. HE AND FERB
ARE UP AT THE MONUMENT.
POSSIBILITIES.
HEY, WHERE'S PERRY?
♪ DOOBY DOOBY DOO BA DOO
♪ DOOBY DOOBY DOO BA
GOOD MORNING, AGENT P.
DR. DOOFENSCHMIRTZ
WE'VE JUST DISCOVERED
HIS NEW HIDEOUT
IS LOCATED INSIDE
LINCOLN'S HEAD AT MT. RUSHMORE.
I--I KNOW.
POOR PLANNING ON OUR PART,
ACTUALLY. SORRY.
PHINEAS!
FERB!
OHH...
HEY, HONEY,
WHAT ARE THEM KIDS
DOING UP ON THE MONUMENT?
LET ME SEE THAT.
[GASPS]
MOM, YOU HAVE GOT TO
SEE THIS NOW.
HERE, LOOK.
OOP. RAN OUT OF TIME.
[MUTTERING]
HERE, LOOK NOW.
OH! OLD RELIABLE GEYSER.
I'M JUST GONNA GO BACK
TO THE GIFT SHOP.
AH, PERRY THE PLATYPUS.
YOUR TIMING IS IMPECCABLE.
AND BY IMPECCABLE, I MEAN
COMPLETELY PECCABLE!
HA HA HA!
YOU ARE JUST IN TIME
TO WITNESS
MY LATEST SCHEME.
BEHOLD!
MY GRIMINATOR!
I WILL BORE A TUNNEL
TO CHINA,
BUILD A TOLL HIGHWAY,
AND MAKE MILLIONS!
SO, AS THEY SAY IN CHINA,
ARRIVEDERCI!
UNH!
AH! OOH!
NOW, WHERE SHOULD WE START?
HI, PHINEAS.
WHATCHA DOIN'?
IT'S A SURPRISE.
WE COULD USE A LOOKOUT.
CAN I HELP?
YOU GOT IT.
[RUSTLING AND CRASHING]
[BIRDS SQUAWKING]
OH, MA'AM,
IF YOU HANDLE
THE BIG STICK,
MOM! YOU'VE GOTTA SEE
WHAT PHINEAS AND FERB
ARE DOING!
UH, EXCUSE ME,
AREN'T YOU BOYS
A LITTLE YOUNG
TO BE RESTORING
A NATIONAL MONUMENT?
YES. YES, WE ARE.
WELL, IT'S GOOD TO SEE
YOUNG PEOPLE
TAKING AN INTEREST
IN OUR NATIONAL HERITAGE.
AAH!
Computer voice:
HULL OVERHEATING.
THE MOLTEN LAVA
OF THE EARTH'S CORE
COMPLETELY SLIPPED MY MIND.
OH, NO! THE LAVA
IS FOLLOWING US!
THE LAVA IS BEING DIVERTED.
YOU DID IT,
PERRY THE PLATYPUS.
YOU SAVED US!
I HATE TO BE A STICKLER,
BUT THE LAVA IS COMING
AGAIN!
Candace: WAIT TILL YOU SEE
WHAT THOSE TWO ARE UP TO.
SHE'S COMING!
SHE'S GETTING CLOSER!
WE'RE RUNNING A LITTLE
BEHIND SCHEDULE.
GO TO PLAN B.
PLAN B, GIRLS!
YOU ARE GOING
TO BE SHOCKED
BY WHAT I'M ABOUT
TO SHOW YOU, MOM.
HMM. I GUESS SOME THINGS
LOOK BETTER IN PHOTOS.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
OH, IT'S DAD.
I FOUND AN ABSOLUTELY
BRILLIANT PARKING SPACE.
GREAT. I'LL MEET YOU
AT THE GIFT SHOP, DEAR.
I STILL HAVE TO BUY
THAT BIG STICK.
[CAW CAW CAW]
HUH?
NOW!
OOPS.
[RUMBLING]
[REOWW!]
HUH?
[GASPS]
OH!
WHY, IT'S--
I-IT'S...
IT'S BEAUTIFUL!
[SOBBING]
MOM!
I GOTTA SHOW YOU
SOMETHING RIGHT NOW!
CANDACE, ARE YOU STILL
TRYING TO GET THE BOYS
IN TROUBLE?
OH, IT'S THE NICEST THING
ANYONE HAS EVER DONE FOR ME!
YOU KNOW, CANDACE,
THIS IS THE SECOND TIME
I'VE CLIMBED UP THERE.
I'M ALREADY DOWN
HALF A DRESS SIZE.
COME ON, HURRY!
AAH!
[ALARM SOUNDS]
HEY, WHERE YOU GOIN'?
AAH!
I DON'T--
[MUTTERING]
HURRY, MOM.
YOU WON'T BELIEVE IT.
HUH?
UCCH.
EEW!
OHH! FINALLY MADE IT,
HONEY.
NOW, WHAT IS IT
YOU WANTED ME TO SEE?
BUT--BUT--
YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, HONEY.
NOW, LET'S GO FIND
YOUR FATHER.
OHH!
[CLANK]
DID YOU LIKE
YOUR BIRTHDAY PRESENT?
UH-HUH. UH.
WELL, IT WAS
DEFINITELY BETTER
THAN THE GORILLA
IN THE CAKE.
I SAW YOU LOOKING AT IT
IN THE GIFT SHOP.
A MT. RUSHMORE
BOBBLEHEAD.
YOU LIKE IT?
OHH! I ABSOLUTELY
LOVE IT.
GREAT.
I GOTTA GET BACK.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
THIS WAS THE BEST
BIRTHDAY EVER.